Free the hostages. Or everyone dies.
Rogue Hostage is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by Jon Keeyes.
A former Marine races against time to save a group of hostages -- including his young
daughter and a congressman — when armed militants take over his stepfather's store.
Kyle Snowden, played by Tyrese Gibson.
Sam Nelson, played by John Malkovich.
Sparks, played by Michael Jai White.
Mikki, played by Holly Taylor.
Sunshine, played by Luna Lauren Vélez.
Eagan, played by Christopher Backus.
Rogue Hostage is a 2021 American action thriller film directed by Jon Keeyes starring
Tyrese Gibson with John Malkovich, Michael Jai White and Christopher Backus.
It was released in the United States on June 11, 2021, by
Vertical Entertainment and Redbox Entertainment.
The tone is intense.